bloggers.com 2010-01-02

# Privacy Policy at Bloggers.com

BLOGGERS ( **BLOGGERS.com** ) operates several websites including BLOGGERS.com. It is **BLOGGERS.com** 's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, **BLOGGERS.com** collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. **BLOGGERS.com** 's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how **BLOGGERS.com** 's visitors use its website. From time to time, **BLOGGERS.com** may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

**BLOGGERS.com** also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. **BLOGGERS.com** does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to **BLOGGERS.com** 's websites choose to interact with **BLOGGERS.com** in ways that require **BLOGGERS.com** to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that **BLOGGERS.com** gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who [PERFORM AN ACTION] at **BLOGGERS.com** to provide [CERTAIN DETAILS]. Those who engage in transactions with **BLOGGERS.com** \- by [DOING SOMETHING], for example - are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, **BLOGGERS.com** collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with **BLOGGERS.com**. **BLOGGERS.com** does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

**BLOGGERS.com** may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, **BLOGGERS.com** may monitor the most popular parts of the [YOUR SITE] site, and [OTHER EXAMPLE]. **BLOGGERS.com** may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, **BLOGGERS.com** does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

**BLOGGERS.com** discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on **BLOGGERS.com** 's behalf or to provide services available at **BLOGGERS.com** 's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using **BLOGGERS.com** 's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. **BLOGGERS.com** will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, **BLOGGERS.com** discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when **BLOGGERS.com** believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of **BLOGGERS.com** , third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a **BLOGGERS.com** website and have supplied your email address, **BLOGGERS.com** may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with **BLOGGERS.com** and our products. We primarily use our [OTHER METHODS, SUCH AS WEB SITE OR BLOGS] to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. **BLOGGERS.com** takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. **BLOGGERS.com** uses cookies to help **BLOGGERS.com** identify and track visitors, their usage of **BLOGGERS.com** website, and their website access preferences. **BLOGGERS.com** visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using **BLOGGERS.com** 's websites, with the drawback that certain features of **BLOGGERS.com** 's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, **BLOGGERS.com** may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in **BLOGGERS.com** 's sole discretion. **BLOGGERS.com** encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
